Habibullah Saleem

Programmer And Developer

Sydney, NSW 2170

040-651-0133

hsaleemdev@gmail.com

A graduate with a Bachelor of Science in Games Development paired with a sub major in Data Analytics. Proficiency in skills including web design & user interaction theory. Main programming languages are C++ and C# but am also experienced in python thanks to my sub major. Operate in a primarily Programming or Quality Assurance role within a team but have developed a series of solo projects with ease. I have completed a wide array of professional and personal projects, available to view at my web portfolio: www.hsaleem.dev



Skills

C#

•

C++

•

Python

T

Unity expertise

•

Unreal Engine expertise

Data Systems

Y

Quality Assurance

React is



Work History

2023-01 - Current

University Tutor (Data Structures and Algorithms)

University Of Technology Sydney, Broadway, Sydney, NSW

- Created plans and communicated deadlines to complete projects and marking on time.
- Learned new skills and applied to daily tasks to improve efficiency and productivity.
- Tutored C++ and several intermediate programming concepts, such as recursion and scalability theory.
- Tutored classes of 20+ students.

2022-07 - 2022-12

2021-11 - 2022-10

2017-06 - 2017-09

2020-01 - 2022-12

Junior Game Developer Intern

Playbox Studios, Paramatta, NSW

- Worked along side a publishing and development team to produce a game.
- Utilized C# to develop object-oriented programming architecture.
- Developed on the Unity engine, with a team of developers, organizing and assigning tasks internally, as well as managing and attending scrums.
- Iteratively progressed through the production of a game, using QA instances to refine and perfect the product.

U@Uni Workshop Mentor

University Of Technology Sydney, Broadway, Sydney, NSW

- Designed teaching curriculum which progressed through core programming principles as well their implementation within games development.
- Taught Unity and C# in a series of workshops.
- Developed tutorials for these workshops, in which programming milestones were tackled through a series of mediums.

Software Analyst

CBIG, Sydney, NSW

- Created customized development frameworks for customers based on specific business goals and budgetary constraints.
- Performed user account maintenance tasks, archiving defunct credentials and monitoring login systems for suspicious trends.
- Worked closely with business users and business analysts to understand functionality and propose creative solutions to meet business needs.



Education

Bachelor of Science: Games Development

University of Technology Sydney - Sydney, NSW



References

Dr. William Raffe Course Coordinator (BSc. Games Development)

Ph: 0437176569

Email: <u>william.raffe@uts.edu.au</u>

Aaima Kusair U@Uni Coordinator

Ph: 0433 512 325

Email: maryam.kausar@uts.edu.au

More references available on request